[
  {
    "question": "Delicious",
    "answer": "おいしい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expensive",
    "answer": "たかい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cheap / Reasonable",
    "answer": "やすい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Good",
    "answer": "いい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "New",
    "answer": "あたらしい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Old",
    "answer": "ふるい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Big",
    "answer": "おおきい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Small",
    "answer": "ちいさい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interesting",
    "answer": "おもしろい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Boring",
    "answer": "つまらない",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Beautiful",
    "answer": "きれい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Famous",
    "answer": "ゆうめい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uncrowded/ Peaceful",
    "answer": "しずか",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Crowded",
    "answer": "にぎやか",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Convenient",
    "answer": "べんり",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unconvenient",
    "answer": "ふべん",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hot",
    "answer": "あつい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cold",
    "answer": "さむい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Warm",
    "answer": "あたたかい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chilly/ Cool",
    "answer": "すずしい",
    "group": "Sprachen\\Japanisch\\Adjektive\\Adjektive - Part 1"
  }
]